[
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q1",
    "question": "Its scientific name is Sedum morganianum.",
    "choices": ["Donkey’s Tail", "Ball Cactus", "Zebra Plant", "Panda Plant"],
    "correct": "Donkey’s Tail"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q2",
    "question": "The color of the leaves of this plant is dark green and can often include red and pink toward the tips of the leaves.",
    "choices": ["Sunburst", "Ox Tongue", "Moonstone", "Ball Cactus"],
    "correct": "Ox Tongue"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q3",
    "question": "A succulent plant that originates from Madagascar and has soft, fuzzy leaves that looks a bit like fur.",
    "choices": ["Jade Plant", "Zebra Plant", "Panda Plant", "Donkey’s Tail"],
    "correct": "Panda Plant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q4",
    "question": "It doesn’t require much pruning and is considered endangered in the wild.",
    "choices": ["Dolphin", "Sunburst", "Moonstone", "Ball Cactus"],
    "correct": "Ball Cactus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q5",
    "question": "It is a branching succulent that forms large rosettes of variegated spoon-shaped leaves at the tip of the branches.",
    "choices": ["Sunburst", "Donkey’s Tail", "Ox Tongue", "Zebra Plant"],
    "correct": "Sunburst"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q6",
    "question": "A succulent that tends to be clustered at the ends of the branch rather than spaced evenly among them.",
    "choices": ["Zebra Plant", "Jade Plant", "Panda Plant", "Dolphin"],
    "correct": "Jade Plant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q7",
    "question": "This plant was created as a hybrid between Senecio rowleyanus and Senecio articulatus.",
    "choices": ["Donkey’s Tail", "Ball Cactus", "Dolphin", "Moonstone"],
    "correct": "Dolphin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q8",
    "question": "It is a popular clump-forming succulent with chubby, pale blue-green to bluish-purple leaves arranged in a rosette at the tips of short stems.",
    "choices": ["Moonstone", "Jade Plant", "Sunburst", "Ball Cactus"],
    "correct": "Moonstone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q9",
    "question": "The most favorable temperature for this succulent is 60 to 80 degrees Fahrenheit.",
    "choices": ["Panda Plant", "Zebra Plant", "Dolphin", "Ox Tongue"],
    "correct": "Zebra Plant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q10",
    "question": "You will only need to repot this plant during spring when the existing pot is too small for it to fit anymore, as it begins to actually bloom when the temperature drops down during the winter. ",
    "choices": ["Donkey’s Tail", "Ball Cactus", "Moonstone", "Jade Plant"],
    "correct": "Donkey’s Tail"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q11",
    "question": "It has a scientific name of Parodia magnifica and it originates from South America",
    "choices": ["Panda Plant", "Sunburst", "Ball Cactus", "Dolphin"],
    "correct": "Ball Cactus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q12",
    "question": "It is an ideal plant for beginners’ gardeners and it is not a fast-growing plant as it will do just fine in the same pot for several years.",
    "choices": ["Jade Plant", "Zebra Plant", "Donkey’s Tail", "Ox Tongue"],
    "correct": "Ox Tongue"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q13",
    "question": "It has a thick, dark green leaves with bumps of white tubercles on the outer surface that are clustered together, hence giving its name.",
    "choices": ["Ball Cactus", "Donkey’s Tail", "Zebra Plant", "Sunburst"],
    "correct": "Zebra Plant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q14",
    "question": "Its leaves are reflective that helps minimize the risk of the plant overheating and produce fuzzy flowers when grown in the wild.",
    "choices": ["Moonstone", "Dolphin", "Panda Plant", "Jade Plant"],
    "correct": "Panda Plant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q15",
    "question": "It can live for a very long time and grow into small trees or shrubs up to 5 feet tall.",
    "choices": ["Ball Cactus", "Jade Plant", "Panda Plant", "Ox Tongue"],
    "correct": "Jade Plant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q16",
    "question": "It should be watered regularly because it has small roots but let it dry completely before watering again.",
    "choices": ["Moonstone", "Donkey’s Tail", "Sunburst", "Zebra Plant"],
    "correct": "Sunburst"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q17",
    "question": "It is a plant that are known to have a fast growth rate.",
    "choices": ["Dolphin", "Jade Plant", "Ball Cactus", "Donkey’s Tail"],
    "correct": "Dolphin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q18",
    "question": "It requires more water during the winter as it is their active growth season.",
    "choices": ["Sunburst", "Moonstone", "Ball Cactus", "Donkey’s Tail"],
    "correct": "Moonstone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q19",
    "question": "It has many short thick succulent branches on a gnarled-looking trunk, suggesting great age even in young specimens.",
    "choices": ["Panda Plant", "Zebra Plant", "Jade Plant", "Dolphin"],
    "correct": "Jade Plant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Succulent",
    "id": "Q20",
    "question": " It tolerates dry period but must be kept moist enough to prevent the leaves from puckering and it is just another novelty plant.",
    "choices": ["Dolphin", "Moonstone", "Sunburst", "Ball Cactus"],
    "correct": "Dolphin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q21",
    "question": "It is one of the most widely-used culinary herbs in the world.",
    "choices": ["Basil", "Oregano", "Rosemary", "Thyme"],
    "correct": "Basil"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q22",
    "question": "Its main components of essential oils are carvacrol and thymol that have antimicrobial properties.",
    "choices": ["Spinach", "Sage", "Oregano", "Thyme"],
    "correct": "Oregano"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q23",
    "question": "It is fairly resistant to most pests and plant diseases, though it is susceptible to certain fungal infections, such as powdery mildew, in humid climates. It is also a common host to spittlebugs.",
    "choices": ["Arugula", "Rosemary", "Marjoram", "Basil"],
    "correct": "Rosemary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q24",
    "question": "It is a low-growing hardy perennial plant that is a fragrant herb with small, leaves and thin, woody stems.",
    "choices": ["Tarragon", "Sage", "Thyme", "Oregano"],
    "correct": "Thyme"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q25",
    "question": "It contains antioxidants which help reduce the risk of serious health conditions like cancer and it’s also rich in vitamin K, which aids the body in clotting blood.",
    "choices": ["Basil", "Marjoram", "Sage", "Tarragon"],
    "correct": "Sage"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q26",
    "question": "It consists of deeply lobed, flat leaves connected to fibrous stems, growing in a loose, basal rosette.",
    "choices": ["Arugula", "Spinach", "Rosemary", "Thyme"],
    "correct": "Arugula"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q27",
    "question": "It tends to grow a bit less aggressively than oregano, and it can’t handle cold weather as well as oregano.",
    "choices": ["Marjoram", "Basil", "Sage", "Tarragon"],
    "correct": "Marjoram"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q28",
    "question": "It has been found that this plant help improve insulin sensitivity and the way your body uses glucose. It’s hardy and easy to grow in a sunny or partially shaded spot in well-drained soil.",
    "choices": ["Thyme", "Tarragon", "Arugula", "Oregano"],
    "correct": "Tarragon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q29",
    "question": "It is a fast-growing plant, yielding many leaves in a short time in the mild weather of spring and fall.",
    "choices": ["Basil", "Rosemary", "Spinach", "Sage"],
    "correct": "Spinach"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q30",
    "question": "Its leaves are glossy and oval-shaped, with smooth or slightly toothed edges that typically cup slightly; the leaves are arranged oppositely along the square stems.",
    "choices": ["Oregano", "Basil", "Thyme", "Arugula"],
    "correct": "Basil"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q31",
    "question": "It is an herb from the mint, or Lamiaceae family. People have used it for thousands of years to add flavor to dishes and to treat health conditions.",
    "choices": ["Marjoram", "Tarragon", "Oregano", "Sage"],
    "correct": "Oregano"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q32",
    "question": "It grows so vigorously in ideal conditions that it needs a yearly pruning to keep it bushy.",
    "choices": ["Rosemary", "Thyme", "Arugula", "Basil"],
    "correct": "Rosemary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q33",
    "question": "It is a wonderful herb with a pleasant, pungent, clover flavor.",
    "choices": ["Sage", "Marjoram", "Thyme", "Spinach"],
    "correct": "Thyme"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q34",
    "question": "It has a scientific name Salvia officinalis and it originates from Southeastern Europe.",
    "choices": ["Tarragon", "Sage", "Basil", "Arugula"],
    "correct": "Sage"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q35",
    "question": "It is a globetrotting garden good that packs a punch for the palette and carries a heavy load of nutrients and minerals for the body.",
    "choices": ["Oregano", "Spinach", "Arugula", "Tarragon"],
    "correct": "Arugula"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q36",
    "question": "The key differences between this plant and oregano are their flowers and flavor. Its flower buds open to white or purple florescence’s, whereas oregano flowers are pink.",
    "choices": ["Basil", "Marjoram", "Thyme", "Rosemary"],
    "correct": "Marjoram"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q37",
    "question": "It is a perennial herb with long, light green leaves and tiny greenish or yellowish white flowers.",
    "choices": ["Tarragon", "Arugula", "Spinach", "Sage"],
    "correct": "Tarragon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q38",
    "question": "When growing this plant, the trick lies in making it last as long as possible, especially in the spring, when lengthening days shorten its life.",
    "choices": ["Basil", "Oregano", "Rosemary", "Spinach"],
    "correct": "Spinach"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q39",
    "question": "It is a perennial shrub and usually grows to about 1 meter long. The linear leaves are about 1 cm long and somewhat resemble small curved pine needles.",
    "choices": ["Tarragon", "Rosemary", "Sage", "Arugula"],
    "correct": "Rosemary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Herb",
    "id": "Q40",
    "question": "This plant is a natural cleaning agent, pesticide, and ritual object. ",
    "choices": ["Sage", "Basil", "Thyme", "Oregano"],
    "correct": "Sage"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q41",
    "question": "They are known for their distinct funnel-shaped or trumpet-shaped petals and prominent central stamens. The flowers can be single or double, depending on the variety.",
    "choices": ["Gumamela", "Plumeria", "Cosmos", "Hollyhocks"],
    "correct": "Gumamela"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q42",
    "question": "They are native to Europe, North America, and some parts of Asia. They have spread to many other regions around the world and can be found in various temperate and subtropical climates.",
    "choices": ["Hollyhocks", "Marigold", "Daisy", "Sunflower"],
    "correct": "Daisy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q43",
    "question": "It typically have thorny stems and compound leaves, with each leaflet having a serrated edge. The flowers come in a diverse range of colors, including red, pink, yellow, white, orange, and lavender.",
    "choices": ["Rose", "Cosmos", "Gumamela", "Plumeria"],
    "correct": "Rose"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q44",
    "question": " Its scientific name is Helianthus annuus.",
    "choices": ["Dahlia", "Marigold", "Sunflower", "Daisy"],
    "correct": "Sunflower"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q45",
    "question": "It also known as frangipani, is native to tropical regions of the Americas, including Mexico, Central America, and the Caribbean.",
    "choices": ["Plumeria", "Rose", "Cosmos", "Hollyhocks"],
    "correct": "Plumeria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q46",
    "question": "This are annual flowering plants known for their vibrant blooms in colors such as yellow, orange, and red. They have a bushy growth habit and reach heights ranging from 6 to 36 inches.",
    "choices": ["Daisy", "Marigold", "Dahlia", "Gumamela"],
    "correct": "Marigold"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q47",
    "question": "It is popular in gardens and landscapes due to their vibrant blooms and ability to attract butterflies and other pollinators. ",
    "choices": ["Cosmos", "Hollyhocks", "Rose", "Sunflower"],
    "correct": "Cosmos"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q48",
    "question": "It is the national flower of Mexico, where it holds cultural and historical significance.",
    "choices": ["Marigold", "Rose", "Dahlia", "Plumeria"],
    "correct": "Dahlia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q49",
    "question": "It is also known by its scientific name Alcea, are believed to be native to Asia and the eastern Mediterranean region.",
    "choices": ["Hollyhocks", "Daisy", "Cosmos", "Sunflower"],
    "correct": "Hollyhocks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q50",
    "question": "It also known as Hibiscus, and is a flowering plant that belongs to the Malvaceae family.",
    "choices": ["Rose", "Marigold", "Gumamela", "Dahlia"],
    "correct": "Gumamela"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q51",
    "question": "The flowers have a yellow disk-like center called the “disk floret” and white or pinkish petals called “ray florets” surrounding the center.",
    "choices": ["Daisy", "Sunflower", "Cosmos", "Plumeria"],
    "correct": "Daisy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q52",
    "question": "This plant are often associated with love, beauty, and romance, making them popular choices for gardens, bouquets, and various celebrations. ",
    "choices": ["Marigold", "Dahlia", "Hollyhocks", "Rose"],
    "correct": "Rose"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q53",
    "question": "This plant is known for their phototropism, a behavior where the flower head follows the movement of the sun throughout the day, facing east in the morning and gradually turning westward as the day progresses. This phenomenon is known as heliotropism.",
    "choices": ["Sunflower", "Daisy", "Gumamela", "Cosmos"],
    "correct": "Sunflower"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q54",
    "question": "In various cultures, it is associated with love, beauty, and spirituality. ",
    "choices": ["Dahlia", "Plumeria", "Rose", "Hollyhocks"],
    "correct": "Plumeria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q55",
    "question": "Its flowers are typically composed of multiple layers of petals arranged in a dense, spherical shape. The petals can be single, semi-double, or double, depending on the variety.",
    "choices": ["Marigold", "Sunflower", "Gumamela", "Daisy"],
    "correct": "Marigold"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q56",
    "question": "t is an annual flowering plants known for their delicate and colorful flowers. They typically have slender stems and fern-like foliage. ",
    "choices": ["Rose", "Hollyhocks", "Cosmos", "Plumeria"],
    "correct": "Cosmos"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q57",
    "question": "This flower is named by Antonio José Cavanilles.",
    "choices": ["Dahlia", "Sunflower", "Plumeria", "Marigold"],
    "correct": "Dahlia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q58",
    "question": "It is usually grown as a biennial, meaning it completes its life cycle within two years. ",
    "choices": ["Rose", "Hollyhocks", "Cosmos", "Daisy"],
    "correct": "Hollyhocks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q59",
    "question": "They are often used in Day of the Dead festivities in Mexico and are associated with good fortune and celebrations in many cultures.",
    "choices": ["Marigold", "Sunflower", "Gumamela", "Dahlia"],
    "correct": "Marigold"
  },
  {
    "category": "Flower",
    "id": "Q60",
    "question": "Its name is derived from the Greek word for 'harmony' or 'beautiful'.",
    "choices": ["Sunflower", "Daisy", "Cosmos", "Plumeria"],
    "correct": "Cosmos"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q61",
    "question": "It has finely divided fronds that resemble tiny fishbones, hence its other common name, Fishbone Fern.",
    "choices": ["Lemon Button", "Silver Lace", "Water Sprite", "Maidenhair"],
    "correct": "Lemon Button"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q62",
    "question": "It known scientifically as Microsorum musifolium, is native to tropical regions of Southeast Asia, including countries like Malaysia, Indonesia, and the Philippines.",
    "choices": ["Asparagus Fern", " Floating Fern", "Crocodile Fern", "Boston Fern"],
    "correct": "Crocodile Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q63",
    "question": "It is a popular indoor fern known for its delicate and lacy foliage. The fronds are finely textured, with a feather-like appearance, consisting of numerous small leaflets arranged along the stem. ",
    "choices": ["Silver Lace", "Asparagus Fern", "Maidenhair", "Floating Fern"],
    "correct": "Silver Lace"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q64",
    "question": "It is known scientifically as Dryopteris erythrosora, is native to East Asia, including regions of China, Japan, and Korea.",
    "choices": ["Water Sprite", "Lemon Button", "Crocodile Fern", "Autumn Fern"],
    "correct": "Autumn Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q65",
    "question": "It is a popular houseplant known for its delicate, feathery foliage and long, arching stems covered with tiny, needle-like leaves called cladophylls.",
    "choices": ["Asparagus Fern", "Maidenhair", "Silver Lace", "Boston Fern"],
    "correct": "Asparagus Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q66",
    "question": "It belongs to the Adiantum genus, which consists of over 200 species found worldwide.",
    "choices": ["Water Sprite", "Maidenhair", "Lemon Button", "Crocodile Fern"],
    "correct": "Maidenhair"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q67",
    "question": "These ferns reproduce and spread through spores or vegetative propagation, allowing them to olonize and cover large areas of water bodies",
    "choices": ["Silver Lace", "Water Sprite", "Floating Fern", "Lemon Button"],
    "correct": "Floating Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q68",
    "question": "It also known as Indian Fern. It is a popular aquatic fern species native to tropical regions in Asia, Africa, and the Americas.",
    "choices": ["Asparagus Fern", "Water Sprite", "Boston Fern", "Autumn Fern"],
    "correct": "Water Sprite"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q69",
    "question": "It is often known as the 'Sword Fern' due to its long, arching fronds that resemble sword blades.",
    "choices": ["Boston Fern", "Lemon Button", "Silver Lace", "Crocodile Fern"],
    "correct": "Boston Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q70",
    "question": "In Feng Shui, they are believed to bring positive energy and vitality to the spaces they inhabit, enhancing the flow of chi (energy) in the home.",
    "choices": ["Floating Fern", "Water Sprite", "Boston Fern", "Crocodile Fern"],
    "correct": "Boston Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q71",
    "question": "It absorbs excess nutrients like nitrates and phosphates, playing a role in reducing algae growth in aquariums.",
    "choices": ["Water Sprite", "Floating Fern", "Silver Lace", "Maidenhair"],
    "correct": "Water Sprite"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q72",
    "question": "The Water Sprite Fern is a fast-growing plant known for its delicate, lacy foliage, which can grow both submerged and emergent.",
    "choices": ["Lemon Button", "Silver Lace", "Floating Fern", "Asparagus Fern"],
    "correct": "Floating Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q73",
    "question": "They are sometimes referred to as 'venus hair fern' or 'lover's fern' due to their connection with matters of the heart.",
    "choices": ["Maidenhair", "Boston Fern", "Crocodile Fern", "Autumn Fern"],
    "correct": "Maidenhair"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q74",
    "question": "They were introduced to horticulture in the 19th century and have since become popular as decorative and ornamental plants due to their delicate, lacy foliage and ease of cultivation.",
    "choices": ["Silver Lace", "Asparagus Fern", "Water Sprite", "Lemon Button"],
    "correct": "Asparagus Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q75",
    "question": "It is commonly called 'Japanese Shield Fern' due to the shape and texture of its fronds resembling a shield.",
    "choices": ["Crocodile Fern", "Silver Lace", "Autumn Fern", "Maidenhair"],
    "correct": "Autumn Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q76",
    "question": "It is also known as the Silver Ribbon Fern due to the striking silver variegation on its fronds.",
    "choices": [" Silver Lace", "Water Sprite", "Boston Fern", "Asparagus Fern"],
    "correct": " Silver Lace"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q77",
    "question": "Its name comes from the unique texture and pattern of its fronds, which resemble the scales of a crocodile.",
    "choices": ["Autumn Fern", "Lemon Button", "Crocodile Fern", "Silver Lace"],
    "correct": "Crocodile Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q78",
    "question": "The fronds are finely textured, feathery, and pinnately divided into small, rounded leaflets, resembling small buttons or coins.",
    "choices": ["Maidenhair", "Lemon Button", "Boston Fern", "Floating Fern"],
    "correct": "Lemon Button"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q79",
    "question": "This fern has a rhizomatous growth habit, meaning it spreads via underground stems called rhizomes.",
    "choices": ["Asparagus Fern", "Silver Lace", "Crocodile Fern", "Water Sprite"],
    "correct": "Crocodile Fern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fern",
    "id": "Q80",
    "question": "It forms a clumping habit and can create a dense, textured mound of foliage. ",
    "choices": ["Autumn Fern", "Floating Fern", "Lemon Button", "Maidenhair"],
    "correct": "Autumn Fern"
  }
]
